# Vikrant Sharma . Jarvis Consulting

Versatile and accomplished Business Analyst with an experience of 4 years in Project Management and 3 years of recent and dedicated experience as a Business Analyst in leading all phases of diverse technology projects for Software and Websoftware development domain clients and specializing in Enterprise IT implementations with sound functional knowledge of process improvement, establishing governance and seamless adoption based on best in class change management processes.

### Skills

Business Skills: Requirement Elicitation, Team Collaboration, Communication and interpersonal skills, BRD/FRD, User Stories, JIRA, Confluence, UML Modelling, BPMN, Use Case, Process Mapping

**Technical Skills:** RDBMS/SQL, Data Modeling/Mapping, Data Analytics, Visio, Lucid Charts, GitHub, Linux, Google Cloud Platform, Sharepoint, Ms Project, POSTgreSQL, SDLC

## Jarvis Projects

Project source code: https://github.com/Jarvis-Consulting-Group/jarvis\_data\_eng-vikrantsharmaJAR

Linux Cluster Resource Monitoring App [GitHub]: Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque lacus. Aliquam varius pulvinar dapibus. Ut a tincidunt sem. Aenean sollicitudin fringilla erat ut imperdiet. Phasellus fermentum, enim vitae laoreet elementum, eros nisl hendrerit lorem.

Python Data Analytics [GitHub]: hi

Hadoop [GitHub]: hi

## **Highlighted Projects**

Web app for restaurant [GitHub]: Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque lacus. Aliquam varius pulvinar dapibus. Ut a tincidunt sem. Aenean sollicitudin fringilla erat ut imperdiet. Phasellus fermentum, enim vitae laoreet elementum, eros nisl hendrerit lorem.

Machine Learning [GitHub]: Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque lacus. Aliquam varius pulvinar dapibus. Ut a tincidunt sem. Aenean sollicitudin fringilla erat ut imperdiet. Phasellus fermentum, enim vitae laoreet elementum, eros nisl hendrerit lorem.

### **Professional Experiences**

Business System Analyst, Jarvis (2022-present): Donec mattis sed justo et sagittis. Vestibulum lacinia nulla ipsum. Curabitur imperdiet nibh vitae leo lacinia laoreet. Nullam accumsan, lectus ut maximus ultricies, augue justo egestas mi, vel bibendum felis.

Business Analyst, VPS Solutions (2021 to 2023): Donec mattis sed justo et sagittis. Vestibulum lacinia nulla ipsum. Curabitur imperdiet nibh vitae leo lacinia laoreet. Nullam accumsan, lectus ut maximus ultricies, augue justo egestas mi, vel bibendum felis.

### Education

Visvesvaraya Technological University (2006-2011), Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science - Scholarship - Dean's List (2015, 2016): Ut enim ad minim veniam - GPA: 3.8/4.0

Conestoga College of Advanced Learning and Technology (2021-2022), Post Graduate Diploma/ Associate Degree, Business Analysis - GPA: 3.8/4.0

### Miscellaneous

- Udacity Machine Learning (2019)
- Winner
- Basketball player; joined xyz club
- Competitive gaming; compete for xyz

• Volunteer, ABC Food bank: Ut enim ad minim veniam